http://www.brynmawrurology.com/privacy-policy

Dr. David McGinnis – Pennsylvania Urologist
Dr. Matt Soroush, M.D. F.A.C.S.
– Pennsylvania Urologist
Dr. James F. Squadrito, Jr., M.D. F.A.C.S. – Pennsylvania Urologist
Team
– Dr. David J. Ellis, M.D. F.A.C.S. – Pennsylvania Urologist
– Dr. David McGinnis – Pennsylvania Urologist
– Dr. Matt Soroush, M.D. F.A.C.S.
– Pennsylvania Urologist
– Dr. James F. Squadrito, Jr., M.D. F.A.C.S. – Pennsylvania Urologist
Privacy Policy
The Bryn Mawr Urology Group respects the privacy of every person visiting our website. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.  We don’t collect personally identifiable information. We do collect cookies which are required for the operation of the site.
Unique Personal Information
Please note that we don’t harvest any info about you!
The Bryn Mawr Urology Group will not collect any personal information about you i.e., your name, address, telephone number, or email address.
General Information Collected Automatically
In some cases, we may collect information that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser, of computer operating system and the domain name of the website from which you linked to The Bryn Mawr Urology Group.
Information We May Automatically Place On Your Computer’s Hard Drive.
The Bryn Mawr Urology Group website will store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “Cookie” or similar file. This information would help us to improve our service we offer in a number of ways.
What is a cookie?
A cookie is a short piece of data, not code, which is sent from a web server to a web browser when that browser visits the server’s site. The cookie is stored on the user’s machine, but it is not an executable program and cannot do anything to your machine. Cookies are required for ASP sites to work properly. They enable the server to tell one user from another. The server doesn’t care about a user’s details–just the fact that one user is different from another.
You can elect to get rid of cookies by going here.
Home
TeamNews
Prostate Cancer
Treatments
Office Location
Appointments
Privacy Policy
In affiliation with:
The Bryn Mawr Urology Group
Rosemont Business Campus
Building One Suite 300
919 Conestoga Road
Rosemont, Pa 19010
tel: 610.525.6580
Click Here to Call on a Smartphone
© 2020 The Bryn Mawr Urology Group.
All rights reserved.
Website Design and Videos Produced by ECP
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Reject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Always Enabled
